Is my car ready yet?
我的汽车修好了吗?
I don't know. sir.
我不知道,先生.
What's the number of your car?
您的汽车牌号是多少?
It is LFZ 312G.
是 LFZ312G.
When did you bring it to us?
您什么时候送来的?
I brought it here three days ago.
3天前.
Ah, yes, I remember now.
啊,是的,我现在记起来了.
Have your mechanics finished yet?
你们的机械师修好了吗?
No, they're still working on it.
没有,他们还在修呢.
Let's go into the garage and have a look at it.
我们到车库去看一下吧.
Isn't that your car?
这难道不是您的车吗?
Well, it was my car.
唔,这曾是我的车.
Didn't you have a crash?
难说您没有出车祸吗?
That's right.
是啊.
I drove it into a lamp-post.
我把汽车撞在电线杆上了.
Can your mechanics repair it?
你们的机械师能修好吗?
Well, they're trying to repair it, sir.
啊,他们正设法修呢,先生.
But to tell you the truth.
不过说实在的,
you need a new car!
您需要一辆新车了!